Previously on Zombieland Saga Revenge!
A few months have passed since our epic fail at EFS,
and we're still not quite over it,
but it seems like a lot of good things are on the horizon for Pran Shushu!
Our Saga Arena concert filled our spirits,
and Lily landed a spot on a national TV talent show!
It's no surprise she made it to the finals,
but she was up against a child acting prodigy
who sang the same song Lily had planned!
Which is, like, the worst thing that could ever happen!
But Lily was such a genius that she improvised a scat arrangement
at the last minute!
It was so amazing that everyone was going
skibbity-ba-ba-ba-dee-ba-doo!
Wee-be-babble-bee-ba-wee-be-dee-babble-bee-
What's with the thousand-yard stare? A new story?
In a few years, you'll have the same look in your eyes.
Everyone has been talking about her online.
That girl looks exactly like Lily Hoshikawa.
They're also picking up on number three and four's likenesses.
After that radio show and Iron Frill calling them rivals,
they're trending like crazy.
Yeah, but most of the posts are jokes about the group
being a collection of doppelgangers.
The more famous you get, the more trolls start to come out.
You were the first one who made the connection
between number four and Junko Kono.
You should have started an expose that second.
I write the facts, not a gossip column.
The only theory I've heard the tracks is that their producer
is intentionally collecting look-alikes.
Wouldn't be surprised if the rest of them were look-alikes, too.
Hey, maybe he raised them from the dead like a bunch of zombies.
Take that trash talk to Mu, the occult mag.
Yes, sir, on my way right now.
Just kiddin'.
It's my lunch break.
As for the rest of them...
Hmmmm.
.
Good morning!
Hello, Mr. Portuttle.
Good morning, sir.
How are my rotten Rockettes?
Gold stars all around for performing the most basic functions of your jobs lately.
Sure, I guess so.
But I've been thinking about it.
We need to aim even higher.
Oh yeah, that's more like it.
And people outside of Saga are starting to talk about us more.
We've got to strike while the iron is hot and get our revenge.
I like your attitude, Saki.
Yeah, we should.
Let's try new stuff.
All right, let's get down to business and talk strategy.
Oh, but wait, we can't do that!
You undead dumbasses have gotten us almost 20 million yen and debt.
Do you think I just have lots of cash coming out of my butt?
We've only gotten the gigs that we had because they were free.
This isn't some very special episode where we learn that money isn't everything.
This is real life!
There's not going to be any revenge or anything else without the ducats, you ding-dongs!
But you're the reason that we're in debt, you idiot!
La la la la la la, Katie!
Quit acting like a child!
Here's the takeaway.
Get off your tails and go earn some of that bread!
I hope you've been paying close attention, Tai!
This is actually her day off, so she's allowed to take a nap!
I'm sorry!
Is she getting paid to sleep?
Come on, ladies!
Put in a little more effort, please!
I didn't raise the walking debt!
Sakura, I sincerely hope you never think that you're a ding-dong.
I won't?
Have a good day!
Bye, Lily!
See you later!
Mm-hmm.
Done.
All right.
Here's today's lift.
Are you sure you can handle this?
Romero did it?
Of course.
Just be careful out there.
You look after her for me, Romero.
What?
Yeah.
Good.
What?
I act like I'm a big-shot writer, yet I can't land a good story.
Not like I'm in Tokyo anymore, but...
It's zero.
Franchishu's number zero.
With all the girls in that group, she still manages to stand out.
For one thing, she doesn't sing, and when she dances, it's to the beat of her own drummer.
She sometimes has these weird outbursts and acts a little nutty, but the other members
act like that's totally normal, and rather than get angry, they seem to find it endearing.
Even weirder, her mysterious behavior has earned her a lot of love amongst their fans.
They think she's adorable.
There's something peculiar about Zero that sets her apart from the rest of these idols.
Hello, Zero.
Are you out shopping today?
I saw that number six on television recently.
She's so talented, I swear.
Ah, you're smelling my fish croquettes.
Do you want one?
Remember not to eat the plastic bag like you did last time.
No.
I did forget about you.
Hmm.
Hey, number Zero, whatcha doin' out here?
Oh, you're doing some grocery shopping today?
Then here.
These cookies will keep you going.
Hmm.
Mm.
Oops.
She hate it!
Crap hide!
I haven't done this in quite some time.
Thank you for shopping.
Oh, I didn't see it was you, Zero.
I saved up enough to get Mommy a new scooter.
No, not Mommy, my mom.
I needed to get her a replacement,
cause her old bike kinda exploded.
Since then, we've been trying to think up new ways to rebrand our team.
What do you think of this?
Our name is Dance Team Dolami!
Could you throw me a bone here?
If you're wondering why we went with a dance team,
watching Number Two perform with Franshushu
inspired us to try something different to shake things up.
All the members got together to talk through our ideas
and decided dancing was our best bet.
Plus, Mommy won't...
I mean, Mom will have less to worry about this way.
Sorry I always start rambling when you come around.
Did you hear anything I've said?
Anyway, our team has some big plans.
One day we're gonna get crazy famous
and perform on the same stage as you.
I can't wait.
How sweet.
I hope they make it some...
She bit the girl's head!
It hurts when you do that!
Ow, stop!
Maria, I see she's chomping your buns again.
Are you ready to go yet?
Is it that time already?
Ow!
Come on, stop, Zero!
We have to make it to 656 Plaza
for the Hisanaka Pharmaceuticals Dance Battle 2019!
We're contestants!
You wanna come with us?
Introducing our next judge!
She's one of the people who made this tournament possible.
You know her from Sagan Ship Z,
the PR manager from Hisanaka Pharmaceuticals!
I hope you enjoy the show and try one of our products.
Woo!
We can do this, girls!
That's right!
Let's rock this joint!
Let's go!
Woo!
Entering the stage, our five-time grand champion, representing Saga, put your hands together
for Coco!
Who is that, what a surprise!
Number Zero, from Fran Shushu!
What the f...
I'm sorry, but the sign-ups for the competition are already closed.
Coco wants to take her on anyway!
Our grand champion's always up for a challenge!
Oh my goodness!
So fast!
Must be causing some kind of optical illusion!
Oh!
So fast!
Must be causing some kind of optical illusion!
Oh!
Ah!
Cook Co is down for the count!
I bet the girls in your group are gonna be stoked to hear about this!
Whoa, don't throw it in the trash!
It's yours!
You earned this cash!
Don't give it to me!
Give me that bag of onions instead!
Why not?!
Whoa, what's the commotion, kiddos?
You've got five seconds to tell me what this is all about.
I'm just trying to get her to take her own money back, officer.
But she's just acting like she couldn't care less even though she won it.
You're telling me you don't know what to do with some cash winnings?
I guess.
Well, well, well.
It's your lucky day, ladies,
because I know exactly what you should do with it.
So, is gambling with minors a normal part of your job?
This policeman's duty is to assist all citizens of Saga!
Seems a little sketchy.
If I let my-
What you doing is pouring them out,
They really popped up.
Hey, my second piece is wall!
Tapi that way!
Anyway, I'm serious.
Hey, man!
I'm trying toplay all the things.
What did I want?
spit and see my 쳤?
информmentation has to save your money today.
And look!
You had indeed rubbish some excitement!
You still have children in the way over there!
Let me tell you that!
Wait, my kids!
Super allora!
not you. Misa. Oh yeah, you might not have heard since you stopped racing bikes. After that game
of chicken with number two, Misa realized she loved the adrenaline. Since then, she's been
thirsty to catch that ultimate rush again, and she finally found it in boat racing.
I see. So she's rebranding like us. The sad thing is, she hasn't won a single race.
Misa keeps screwing it up. It's always the same. She accelerates at the wrong time
and wipes out. When she first started, people called her the runaway princess. Then they
changed their tune and started cracking jokes, saying she was a total loser. Now everyone
calls her Misa the warthog. Try not to crash and burn out there.
That's pathetic. You want to eat those words? If Misa makes some dumb mistake in this race
while I'm watching, I'll kill her myself. Let's head to the bookie. We've got a round
that we can bet on it. All right. If you want something big, cut me in.
Sir. Hello, sir. Over. Where have you been? Well, I've been, uh, doing real police stuff.
Just like I'm supposed to be. Are you at the horse track? No, it's definitely not that track.
Exactly. She eats everything.
Maybe I'm just tired.
I'm not lying to you, sir. No, I'm not at the horse track.
Sure, horses are magical beasts, but I'm not anywhere near one now. I swear.
Zero, there you are. Hey, we've got seats down here.
All right. It's starting up. I wonder how Misa the warthog is going to do today.
She's got a lot of guts, but who those turns of hers.
Maria?
You can do it, Misa!
Yeah! All right! That's how you do it! Nice job!
I hope you're watching, Maria. Eat your heart out!
Number two.
Coming through!
She did it!
That was amazing!
Holy crap! She did it! Wow! She pulled off the legendary Eel Gobi turn.
I can't believe it! It's been forever since I've seen one!
The Eel Gobi has returned to Kuratsu!
That was a damn fine race. I couldn't take my eyes off of it.
It might not have been the horse track, but that was still an awesome throwdown!
Why didn't I bet on it?
Which racer did you bet on number zero?
No. Holy...
She wants so much money!
Ah!
Really?
Oh my God!
I've followed that girl around all damn day.
But instead of getting any answers, I have even more questions and nothing to show for it.
I give up.
There you are!
Whoa! It's Maria!
We were worried you got lost or something.
What happened?
I love it!
Thank you, dear.
You did a great job.
Hey, number two.
It's nice to see you!
Hi!
Good to see you too.
What are you doing here?
Uh, number zero came into the supermarket and then,
man, a whole boatload of stuff happened.
Here, check this out.
Zero won 20 million at the boat races.
One bet.
Are you serious?
She won that money?
Whoa, 20 million yen.
That's some serious bankroll, right?
What does this mean for us, you guys?
So if she actually won that money and it's ours, then we can pay off our debt.
It's Ty.
I mean number zero.
Let's go tell Kotaro, okay?
Now!
Number two?
That'll do, girls.
That'll do.
All right!
No!
That ended up being quite the interesting thing.
Damn, Ty, boy to stick it to Mr. Sunglasses like a champ.
You tape us!
Thank you, Ty!
For real though, is there a lot of surprise to us?
I give up
We were worried you got lost or something
What happened?
Tai, I mean number zero
Let's go tell Kotaro, okay?
Now
Hey, maybe he raised him from the dead
Like a bunch of zombies
It's me, Sakura
You can never tell which way things will turn out, huh?
Just like I never thought I'd be a zombie
Next time on Zombieland Saga Revenge Episode 7
My My Revolution Saga
Oh my, what's gonna happen this time?